("Baby")
♪ Ooh whoa ♪
♪ You know you love
me, I know you care ♪
♪ Just shout whenever
and I'll be there ♪
♪ You are my love,
you are my heart ♪
♪ And we will never,
ever, ever be apart ♪
♪ Are we an item ♪
♪ Girl quit playin' ♪
♪ We're just friends,
what are you sayin' ♪
♪ Said there's another and
look right in my eyes ♪
♪ My first love broke my
heart for the first time ♪
♪ And I was like
baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby no ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ I thought you'd
always be mine, mine ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby no ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby ooh ♪
♪ I thought you'd
always be mine, mine ♪
♪ Oh for you, I would
have done whatever ♪
♪ And I just can't believe
we ain't together ♪
♪ And I wanna play it cool ♪
♪ But I'm losin' you ♪
♪ I'll buy you anything ♪
♪ I'll buy you any ring ♪
♪ And I'm in pieces,
baby fix me ♪
♪ And just shake me, 'til you
wake me from this bad dream ♪
♪ I'm goin' down,
down, down, down ♪
♪ And I can't just believe my
first love won't be around ♪
♪ And I'm like baby,
baby, baby oh ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby no ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ I thought you'd
always be mine, mine ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby no ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby ooh ♪
♪ I thought you'd
always be mine, mine ♪
♪ Luda, when I was 13,
I had my first love ♪
♪ There was nobody that
compared to my baby ♪
♪ And nobody came between us,
no one could ever come above ♪
♪ She had me goin' crazy ♪
♪ Oh, I was starstruck ♪
♪ She woke me up daily ♪
♪ Don't need no Starbucks ♪
♪ She made my heart pound ♪
♪ And skip a beat when I
see her in the street and ♪
♪ At school on the playground ♪
♪ But I really wanna
see her on the weekend ♪
♪ She know she got me dazin' ♪
♪ 'Cause she was so amazin' ♪
♪ And now my heart is breakin' ♪
♪ But I just keep on sayin' ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby no ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ I thought you'd
always be mine, mine ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby oh ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby no ♪
♪ Like baby, baby, baby ooh ♪
♪ I thought you'd
always be mine, mine ♪
♪ Now I'm gone ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
now I'm all gone ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
now I'm all gone ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
now I'm all gone ♪
♪ Gone, gone, I'm gone ♪
♪♪♪